itsallgay.com 2010-08-08

# Its All Gay

### www.itsallgay.com Privacy Policy

Your right to privacy is important to us

Our third party licensors are fully registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and aim to comply with all the protection the Act affords to you. Further information on the Act is on the internet at www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk. The data protection registration is held under the name of GLBT Limited. Under the Data Protection Act 1998, we have a legal duty to protect any personal information we collect from you. Save for information being passed on between us and our third party licensors, we do not pass or sell on your details to any third party unless you give us permission to do so or the law requires/permits it. 

#### User Provided Information -

You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name, email and in some cases mailing address) to itsallgay when choosing to participate in various activities on the itsallgay Website such as uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the photo/video comments section, entering contests or competitions, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

#### Cookies Information -

When you visit the itsallgay Website, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. itsallgay uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the itsallgay Website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

#### Log File Information -

When you visit the itsallgay Website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

#### Where your information is held -

Your information is held on our servers and our servers are based in Amsterdam. We must advise that the security is not as good as a service provider based here in the United Kingdom. However, we do have security measures in place with the service providers that host our servers to offer some level of protection of your data. 

#### The Way itsallgay Uses Information -

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the itsallgay Webite, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the itsallgay Website.  
Any personal information or photo/video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the itsallgay Website and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the itsallgay Website may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.  
We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major itsallgay Website changes or for customer service purposes).  
We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, click stream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the itsallgay Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analysing User preferences and trends.  
We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the itsallgay Website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

#### When itsallgay Discloses Information :

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.  
We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the itsallgay Website.  
We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with the Laws of England & Wales.  
itsallgay also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that itsallgay believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the itsallgay Website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of itsallgay, our users or others.
